thefinanceguardian.com 2013-05-03

# Privacy Policy

This is a privacy policy for thefinanceguardian.com who respects your privacy.  We are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors  while they interact with the content, products and services on this site. This Privacy Policy applies to this Site only. It does not apply to other websites to which we link.  Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want you to understand what information we collect about you, how we collect it, how that information is used, and how you can control our disclosure of it. You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

**1)   Information Collected**

We collect two types of information from you: i) information that you voluntarily provide to us (e.g. through a voluntary registration process, sign-ups or emails); and ii) information that is derived through automated tracking mechanisms.

Voluntary Information for Services and Features: 

We [also] collect personally identifiable information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site, including: i) consenting to receive email about upcoming promotions or events, ii) consenting to receive email. ** __** When you choose to use these additional features, we require you to provide your “Contact Information” in addition to other personal information that may be required to complete a transaction. Occasionally, we may also request information such as your shopping preferences and demographics which will help us better serve you and our others users in the future. 

Cookies:

Our site uses "cookies" and other tracking technologies.  Cookies enable us to track how were visitors come from and how they interact with our site.  When you visit our site items such as your IP address, browser & version, operating system, date & time, and the site from which you came are stored in a log file and/or database.  Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, certain functions of this website may not work properly.

Third-Party Cookies:  In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**3)   How We Use Your Information**

** thefinanceguardian.com ** only uses your personal information for the original purposes it was given. Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection.

** thefinanceguardian.com ** will not disclose, use, give or sell any personal information to third parties for any purposes other than to our suppliers and other third parties who need to know in order to deliver services on behalf of **thefinanceguardian.com** unless required to do so by law. Further, **thefinanceguardian.com** reserves the right to contact you regarding matters relevant to the underlying service provided and/or the information collected.

Please note that personally identifiable information is used only to provide you with a more enjoyable, convenient online experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: providing customer service; tracking your activity; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site. 

**thefinanceguardian.com** may use your personal information for target advertising toward you based on things such as region, gender, interests, goals, habits, etc.

We may permit certain trusted third parties to track usage, analyze data such as the source address that a page request is coming from, your IP address or domain name, the date and time of the page request, the referring Web site (if any) and other parameters in the URL. This is collected in order to better understand our Web site usage, and enhance the performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. We may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.

Also, we may share personally identifiable or other information with our parent, subsidiaries, divisions, and affiliates.

We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control.  We also reserve the right to transfer any data collected in the event of an acquisition, full or partial, of the company or its assets.

**thefinanceguardian.com** may disclose Contact Information in special cases where we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. 

You will receive notice when your personally identifiable information might be provided to any third party for any reason other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you will have an opportunity to request that we not share such information.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

**4) How We Protect Your Information**

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We take appropriate security measures to protect your information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information and data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

**5) Third Party Advertising** __

Advertisements appearing on this Site may be delivered to you by one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the advertising partners to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising partner to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. **thefinanceguardian.com** does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertising servers of ad partners.   This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by **thefinanceguardian.com** and does not cover the use of cookies by any of its advertisers. 

**6) Other Sites** __

Other sites accessible through our Sites have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Please be aware that our Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linked to our Sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit Personal Information. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our Sites may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. 

On behalf of various sponsors, we may provide sponsored links to third-party websites. If you click on a sponsored link or banner ad, a "window" or "frame" containing a third-party's web site may appear in the foreground with a Site in the background. Unless you are on one of our Sites, any time that you have moved to a window, you should assume that your Personal Information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the windowed or framed site's privacy policy (if any). 

**7) Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences**

We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personal information for many of our services.  If you are a registered user, you may access and update your registration information and your preferences to receive email or other communications from us by sending an email to info@thefinanceguardian.com. 

**8) Email Choice/Opt-out**

If any user who receives an email from the Site and would prefer not to receive such communications in the future, [he or she] can do so by following the instructions in the emails.  In addition, you may send an email to info@thefinanceguardian.com. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications from us for up to ten business days as we process your request.

**9) Children's Privacy and Parental Controls**

We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that can be used to prevent children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

**10) Disclaimer to Security**

By consenting to the Terms and Conditions of the Site and hence the Privacy Policy, you consent that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk.

**11) Notification of Changes**

**thefinanceguardian.com** reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. If at some point in the future, there is a change to our Privacy Policy, unless we obtain your express consent, such change will only apply to information collected after the revised Privacy Policy took effect. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

** 12)  CONTACT INFORMATION:**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact:

** thefinanceguardian.com**

**info@thefinanceguardian.com**
